Pharos: Lighting the Path to Understanding UP250
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Pharos: Lighting the Path to Understanding
2002 -- 2012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies
UP250
0.5 Linear Feet
11 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Newsletter of the Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies at Tufts University, which is printed each Fall. This collection contains the full run of the Pharos newsletter in print and digital formats.
Biographical / Historical
In 1991, Fares I. Fares, a trustee and member of Tufts' International Board of Overseers and the Board of Overseers for Arts and Sciences and the son of former trustee Issam M. Fares (Deputy Prime Minister of Lebanon), first conceived of a lectures series to further understanding of the issues facing the Middle East. Today, the Issam M. Fares Lecture Series is the fulfillment of that idea. The lecture series is supported by an endowment from the Fares Foundation that enables Tufts University to implement a program for promoting Middle Eastern studies in the humanities, social sciences, and arts, including history, political science, economics, sociology, anthropology, demographic studies, and languages.
- Pharos: Lighting the Path to Understanding, 2002 -- 2012; UP250.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 11 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Pharos: Lighting the Path to Understanding, the newsletter of the Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies at Tufts University. Pharos is printed each Fall.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Pharos, 2002; UP250.001.001.00001; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
    Fares Research Center
  - Pharos, 2003; UP250.001.001.00002; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2004; UP250.001.001.00003; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2005; UP250.001.001.00004; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2006; UP250.001.001.00005; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2007; UP250.001.001.00006; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2008; UP250.001.001.00007; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2009; UP250.001.001.00008; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2010; UP250.001.001.00009; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2011; UP250.001.001.00010; Fares Center for Eastern Mediterranean Studies (Box 1)
  - Pharos, 2012; UP250.001.001.00011